And just like that, we're back.
2024.
I am starting this year very different than I started last year.
I'm starting this year with no man, no agents.
But I am starting this year with shows.
Yeah, girl is back on the road.
They tried to hold me down.
I'm back up in this bed.
No weapon formed against me.
2024 is going to be a doozy,
which was why I felt it was so imperative that I get back in front of y'all
in a physical, live sense.
First stop, Chicago, January 19th and 20th at the Den Theater.
And yes, I'm in actual Chicago this time.
I ain't out there in Schaumburg.
So I'll be doing standup.
You need the jokes.
Who would have thunk that I'd need anti-Zionist material?
But it is available.
I told you 2024 is starting off different.
I'll also be doing these political forums called In a Man Who We Trust Live
where you're going to get information, comedy, community.
We'll do trivia that teaches us.
We will get knowledge that empowers us
because maybe we don't know enough and we need to teach each other.
So get your tickets.
If you love me.
If you love me, buy them.
At amandaseals.com.
Chicago's up first in two weeks.
Coming up, we'll have Dallas.
We'll have Toronto.
We'll have Stanford, Connecticut, and more.
Sign up for my newsletter so that you're not left out.
Y'all, we're going to need each other this year.
Get your tickets at amandaseals.com.
Thank you.
Shukran.
Gracias.
We need to be global this year, y'all.
All in together.